Finding Aid for the Annie P. Ransom Collection
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Annie P. Ransom Collection
1878-1965
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0356
.42 linear feet
Scope and Contents
This collection contains correspondence, a diary, a daily devotional book, newspaper clippings, and hospital insurance papers belonging to Annie P. Ransom, daughter of John Crowe Ransom.
- Bank Statements
  - 1964
- Correspondence
  - February 2, 1965 – from John Crowe Ransom
- Daily Devotional
  - ‘Daily Food for Christians’ - 1888
- Diary
  - 1878
- Hospital Insurance Papers
  - 1965
- Newspaper Clippings
  - n.d.